A Guide to the Virginia Department of Treasury, Division of Unclaimed Property, 1822-1991
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Department of Treasury, Division of Unclaimed Property, 1822-1991
The Library of Virginia
31473, 32981, 42943, 43250, 50624, 52072, 52014, 52086
23.59 cu ft (60 boxes and 2 volumes)
Virginia. Department of Treasury.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected information closed for [x] years after date record created. Restrictions vary. See individual catalogue records for nature of restriction.
Acquisition Information
Virginia Department of Treasury, Division of Unclaimed Property, 101 North 14th Street, Richmond, VA 23219, transferred 9 June 1982 (accessions 31473 and 32981); Accession 42943 transferred 2 November 2006 and accessioned 6 November 2006; Accession 43250 transferred 14 May 2007 and accessioned 7 June 2007; Accession 50624 transferred 3 October 2012 and accessioned 8 November 2012; Accession 52072 transferred 23 August 2017 and accessioned 30 August 2017; Accession 52086 transferred 8 September 2017 and accessioned 12 September 2017.
Historical Information
The Treasurer is the custodian of the property presumed abandoned and remitted to the State's custody for safekeeping. The property is retained by the Treasurer after being declared unclaimed property, for eventual delivery to persons claiming an interest in such property pursuant to Sections 55-210.20 through 55-210.22 of the Code of Virginia. Per LVA schedule 152-006, records are retained by the Dept. of Treasury for 20 years and then transferred to the Library of Virginia.
Scope and Content
Each unclaimed property lot has been catalogued separately.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged by accession and then by lot number.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Bona vacantia.; Cemeteries.; Contracts.; Courts-martial and courts of inquiry.; Court records.; Divorce.; Draft registration.; Escheat.; Equity.; Insurance, Fire.; Insurance, Life.; Insurance policies.; Insurance, Title.; Land title -- Registration and transfer.; Letters (correspondence).; Liens.; Maps.; Military discharge.; Personal property.; Powers of attorney.; Unclaimed estates.
Corporate Names:
Virginia. Department of the Treasury. Division of Unclaimed Property; Virginia. Treasurer's Office.
Genre and Form Terms:
Abstracts of title.; Account books.; Agreements.; Appraisals.; Articles of incorporation.; Baptismal certificates.; Bill of sale.; Birth certificates.; Birth records.; Briefs (legal documents).; Certificates of incorporation.; Chancery cases.; Checks.; Civil court records.; Clippings.; Contracts.; Correspondence.; Death certificates.; Declarations.; Deeds.; Design patents.; Discharges.; Divorce records.; Drivers' licenses.; Estate records.; Financial statements.; Identity cards.; Indentures.; Insurance policies.; Invoices.; Journals (accounts).; Leases.; Ledgers (account books).; Legal documents.; Letters (correspondence).; Membership cards.; Memorandums.; Military records.; Minutes.; Mortgages.; Naturalization records.; Obituaries.; Photographs.; Plats.; Powers of attorney.; Receipts.; Registrations (licenses).; State government records.; Telegrams.; Transcripts.; Wills.
Contents List
- Records - Accession 31473, 1830-1962., Extent: 22 boxes. (Box 1-22)
  By lot number
  - Lot 101 - Articles of Agreement,1908. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lot 102 - Deeds, Insurance Policies, Surveys1900-1904. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lot 103 - Correspondence,1907-1908. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lot 104 Deed of Trust,1927. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lot 105 - Insurance Policy,1933. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Lots 106-108 - Bushrod W. Lynn Papers, Civil War materials,1862-1865. (1 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Lots 106-108 - Bushrod W. Lynn Papers, Correspondence,1891-1911 (2 of 4). (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Lots 106-108 - Bushrod W. Lynn Papers, Deeds,1869-1908. (3 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lots 106-108 - Bushrod W. Lynn Papers, Miscellaneous,1900-1909. (4 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lot 109 - Deeds, John A. Marshall,1865-1912. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lot 111 - Papers, S. Vavener Moore,1918-1927. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lot 112 - Papers, John E. Murphy,1893-1929. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lot 113 - Deed, Fred W. Olsen,1922. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Lot 116 - Deeds, Egbert A. Thompson,1908-1910. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Lot 117 - Papers, Alexander J. Wedderburn,1890-1910. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Lot 131 - Insurance policies, George L. Birch,1936-1939. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Lot 132 - Papers, Alice Lorraine Jones,1941-1943. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Lot 133 - Papers, Alfred K. Gilman,1925-1935. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Lot 135 - Papers, Eleanor M. Diane,1927-1930. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Lot 136 - Papers, Richard T. Mannhardt,1936-1937. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Lot 137 - Papers, Odie R. Howell,1918-1926. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Lot 138 - J. W. Baker,1899-1921. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Lot 139 - Papers, English K. Beacham, Nora Thompson Churchill, Jack Thompson1912-1916. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Lot 140 - Deeds, William G. Bryon,1915-1918. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Lot 142 - Papers, R. W. Conrad,1918-1921. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Lot 146 - Insurance policies, Arne Sorum,1923-1924. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Lot 147 - Papers, Thomas Garland Westbrook,1919-1945. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Lot 148 - Will, William Oscar Heath,1925. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Lot 150 - Grant H. Loser,1927. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Lot 151 - Papers, Bruce McIntyre,1915-1922. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Lot 152 - Papers, Jesse Thomas Miller,1913-1920. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Lot 153 - Papers, Winslow H. Miner,1908-1921. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Lot 154 - Will, Charles Clay Mitchell,1907. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Lot 155 - Dissolution of partnership, Robert Waitt,1939. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Lot 159 - Insurance policy, S. P. Sawyer,1934. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Lot 160 - Agreement, John W. Gates,1934. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Lot 161 - Letter, Eugene Jones,1934. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Lot 162 - Papers, Edgar B. Allen,1901-1922. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Lot 163 - Papers, William Melvin Oakley,1937-1979. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Lot 165 - Deeds, Bert A. Denicker and Geoffrey Chapman,1937-1939. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Lot 166 - Papers, James Hodges Collie,1924-1929. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Lot 168 - Papers, Thomas R. Brumfield and Posie L. Hines,1892-1927. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lot 170 - Papers, W. S. Morrison,1908-1927. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lot 172 - Papers, Oscar L. Farrow,1916-1927. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Lot 173 - Papers, Joseph D. Rosenberg,1919-1920. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Lot 195 - Papers, Elizabeth J. Roberts,1919-1930. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Lot 197 - Papers, Percy S. Vaughan,1924-1926. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Lot 198 - Patents, William Burlingham,1915-1916. (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Lot 198 - Patents, William Burlingham,1915-1916. (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Lot 199 - Insurance policies, Pattie Barksdale Vaughan,1942. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Lot 200 - Papers, Mrs. L. L. Wilson,1916-1927. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Lot 201 - Insurance policy, John T. Bousman,1917-1962. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Lot 203 - Papers, S. J. Hoskins,1919-1920. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Lot 206 - Papers, Richard B. Fentress,1888-1907. (1 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Lot 206 - Papers, Richard B. Fentress,1888-1907. (2 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Lot 206 - Papers, Richard B. Fentress,1888-1907. (3 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Lot 207 - William H. Megee, Jr., Diaries,1913-1918. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Lot 209 - Samuel Carlisle Davidson Papers,1905-1912. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Lot 211 - Larus Family Papers,1865-1927. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Lot 213 - Smith Family Papers, Deeds,1842-1914. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Lot 213 - Smith Family Papers, Insurance Policies,1907-1914. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Lot 213 - Smith Family Papers, Miscellaneous,1898-1914. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Lot 214 - Spain-Wilkerson Papers,1918-1926. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Lot 218 - MacPhail Family Papers,1925-1935. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Lot 220 - Deed, Fannie V. Blount to Aimee M. Pratt,1932. (See also oversized Box 21) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Lot 221 - Robertson Family Papers, Correspondence,1835-1874. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Lot 221 - Robertson Family Papers, Deeds,1833-1866. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Lot 221 - Robertson Family Papers, Insurance Policies,1836-1893. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Lot 221 - Robertson Family Papers, Miscellaneous,1832-1874. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Lot 221 - Robertson Family Papers, Receipts,1850-1891. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Lot 208 - Coastwise Dredging Company, Bills of Sale,1910-1911. (See also oversized Box 21) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Lot 208 - Coastwise Dredging Company, Contracts,1902-1910. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Lot 208 - Coastwise Dredging Company, Contracts,1911. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Lot 208 - Coastwise Dredging Company, Contracts,1912-1913. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Lot 208 - Coastwise Dredging Company, Insurance,1902, 1913-1914. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Lot 208 - Coastwise Dredging Company, Libel Suit,c. 1908. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Lot 208 - Coastwise Dredging Company, Mortgages,1912. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Lot 208 - Coastwise Dredging Company, Releases,1911-1913. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Lot 208 - Coastwise Dredging Company, Scow #22,1910. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Lot 208 - Coastwise Dredging Company, Steam Yacht "Chetolah" Wreck Report,1911. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Lot 222 - Zaidee B. Rogers Papers, Correspondence-Alfred B. Baldwin,1915-1916. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Lot 222 - Zaidee B. Rogers Papers, Correspondence-Addison Ely,1909-1910. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Lot 222 - Zaidee B. Rogers Papers, Correspondence-Miscellaneous,1906-1916. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lot 222 - Zaidee B. Rogers Papers, Correspondence-Benjamin H. Rogers,1909-1917. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Lot 222 - Zaidee B. Rogers Papers, Correspondence-Jacob Veenstra,1914. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Lot 222 - Zaidee B. Rogers Papers, Miscellaneous,1904-1905. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Lot 222 - Zaidee B. Rogers Papers, Photographs,1888. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Lot 227 - Mary R. Wilcox Papers,1860-1906. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Lot 230 - G. Landon Papers,1929. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Lot 231 - Wesley A. Baker, Fire Insurance Policy,1935-1938. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Lot 232 - Alice L. Heller - Fire Insurance Policies,1938-1940. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Lot 233 - Lula L. Peer, Contract,1936. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Lot 248 - Harrison Family Papers,1830-1889. (1 of 5) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Lot 248 - Harrison Family Papers,1830-1889. (2 of 5) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Lot 248 - Harrison Family Papers,1830-1889. (3 of 5) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Lot 248 - Harrison Family Papers,1830-1889. (4 of 5) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Lot 248 - Harrison Family Papers,1830-1889. (5 of 5) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Lot 249 - Letter,14 April 1932. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Lot 252 - Prophytol Products Company, Inc., Records,1914. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Lot 253 - Fire Insurance Policy,1923. (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Lot 254 - Chalkley Family Papers,1876-1883. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Lot 247 - Business Papers,1873-1910. (1 of 6) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Lot 247 - Business Papers,1873-1910. (2 of 6) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Lot 247 - Business Papers,1873-1910. (3 of 6) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Lot 247 - Business Papers,1873-1910. (4 of 6) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Lot 247 - Business Papers,1873-1910. (5 of 6) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Lot 247 - Business Papers,1873-1910. (6 of 6) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Lot 255 - Robinson Family Papers,1836-1886. (1 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Lot 255 - Robinson Family Papers,1836-1886. (2 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Lot 255 - Robinson Family Papers,1836-1886. (3 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Lot 255 - Robinson Family Papers,1836-1886. (4 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Lot 255 - Robinson Family Papers,1836-1886. (5 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Lot 257 - Evan Robinson Alphin Papers,1913-1915. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Lot 260 - Certificate of Incorporation & Fire Insurance Policy,1923. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Lot 261 - Henry T. Barnum Papers,1914-1917. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Lot 262 - Barrow Family Papers,1914-1926. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Lot 263 - Mildred W. Bear Papers,1934-1936. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Lot 268 - Absalom Blackburn Papers,1910-1912. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Lot 270 - Cost Reports and Vouchers,1879-1883. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Lot 271 - Military Discharge of Charles C. Bodeker,1905. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Lot 272 - Deed,1913. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Lot 273 - Disability Insurance Policies,1937. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Lot 274 - William W. Brauer Papers,1891-1892. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Lot 275 - Fire Insurance Policy,1923. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Lot 276 - Life Insurance Policy,1931. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Lot 279 - Deed,1915. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Lot 280 - Agreement,1918. (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Lot 281 - Patent,1926. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Lot 286 - West Ginter Park Realty Corporation Papers,1916-1924. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Lot 291 - Will,1925. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Lot 294 - James T. Cosby Papers,1925. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Lot 296 - William S. Croxton Papers,1881-1913. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Lot 297 - Ousby R. Cunningham Papers,1926-1929. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Lot 298 - Franklin P. Curtis Papers,1915-1934. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Lot 299 - Frederick R. Dapprich Papers,1911-1913. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Lot 301 - Deed of Lease,1910. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Lot 305 - James K. Eagle Papers,1907-1911. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Lot 306 - Faisom Family Papers,1928-1931. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Lot 307 - Correspondence of James Eugene Gravatte,1899-1901. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Lot 309- H. C. Haile Papers,1935-1938. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Lot 310 - Will of Edward Matthew Hall,1917. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Lot 311 - Deed of Trust to C. H. Sutton,1895. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Lot 312 - Henry C. Hechler Papers,1900-1913. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Lot 313- Isabel S. Hill Papers,1907-1925. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Lot 314 - Notes and Protests,1907. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Lot 315 - C. E. Hughes Papers,1914. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Lot 316 - Insurance Papers of Hunter Russell Hughes,1917-1918. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Lot 317 - Letter to W. C. Hurley,1926. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Lot 318 - Iron Gate Land & Improvement Company Records,1889-1893. (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Lot 319 - James River Granite Corp., Agreement,1908. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Lot 320 - R. Kastleberg Sons Papers,1917. (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Lot 323 - J. M. Lewis Papers,1874-1876. (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Lot 325 - Lottner Family Papers,1846-1908. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Lot 326 - Insurance Policy,1930. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Lot 327 - M. M. Martin Papers,1900-1906. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Lot 328 - Photographs,n.d.. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Lot 329 - Mills Family Papers,1904-1937. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Lot 330 - Fire Insurance Policy, H. G. Mills,1926. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Lot 332 - Schussler Family Papers,1916-1926. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Lot 335 - Robert H. Morrison Papers,1918-1920. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Lot 337 - William Gray Moseley Papers,1902. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Lot 338 - Life Insurance Policies,1919-1924. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Lot 342 - New York & Pennsylvania Coal and Coke Company Records,1916-1919. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Lot 343 - Thomas W. Nolde Papers,1920-1926. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Lot 346 - William Henry White Papers,1913-1915. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Lot 347 - Mayo Ross Palmore Papers,1913-1915. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Lot 349 - Ruth Nimmo White Phillips Papers,1916-1938. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Lot 351 - Deed,1905. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Lot 352 - John D. Potts, Jr., Papers,1903-1931. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Lot 357 - Deed,1898. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Lot 358 - Samuel P. Ratner Papers,1913-1921. (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Lot 359 - Margaret Jennings Reid Papers,1916-1917. (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Lot 361 - Insurance Policy,1938. (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Lot 387 - Eugene W. Hoge Papers,1871-1872. (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Lot 389 - Correspondence,1921. (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Lot 391 - Abstract of Title,1925. (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Lot 392 - St. John Family Papers,1880-1904. (See also oversized Box 21) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Lot 393 - Steiner Family Papers,1920-1921. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Lot 395 - Receipt from Settlement, William E. Tanner,1896. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Lot 397 - Life Insurance Policies, Robert Thomas,1931-1933. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Lot 399 - Life Insurance Policy, William Harold Thompkins Jr.,1923. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Lot 400 - James Turner Papers,1934-1940. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Lot 401 - Deed and Receipt, H. M. Vaughan,1915. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Lot 403 - Frank T. West Jr. Papers,1917-1923. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Lot 405 - Mary A. Whitlock Papers,1932-1934. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Lot 406 - Charles R. Winfree Papers,1916-1925. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Lot 409 - O. M. Woodward Papers,1892-1912. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Lot 412 - Deeds,1928-1933. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Lot 413 - Identification Tag, L. R. Oliver,n.d.. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Lot 436 - Joseph C. Blanton Papers,1928-1929. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Lot 437 - Letter, Virginia Bridges,n.d.. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Lot 438 - Fire Insurance Policies, John Jesse Kellam,1921. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Lot 439 - Larrimore Family Papers,1912-1918. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Lot 440 - Ernest May Papers,1917-1921. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Lot 441 - George A. Patterson Papers,1924-1928. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Lot 442 - Peninsula Barbecue Records,1929-1931. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Lot 443 - Miras Brothers Papers,1918-1919. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Lot 444 - David A. Dutrow Papers,1906-1916. (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Lot 445 - L. D. Kitchens Papers,1943. (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Lot 452 - C. Manning Plumbing Co. Records,1928. (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Lot 453 - Grant Family Papers,1892-1927. (See also oversized Box 21) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Lot 460 - Edwin R. Harris Papers,1915-1926. (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Lot 461 - William J. Jackson Papers,1920-1927. (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Lot 462 - Fire Insurance Policy,1928. (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Lot 482 - Bond, James A. Boyd,1880. (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Lot 485 - E. R. Rhodes Papers,1934-1936. (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Lot 486 - Deed of Trust,1929. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Lot 490 - Custer Chemical Corp. Records,1926-1930. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Lot 493 - Emery Dorman Records,1918-1925. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Lot 494 - Honorable Discharge, Harry A. Harkness,1943. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Lot 496 - Will, Catherine C. Hodge,1934. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Lot 497 - Certificates of Membership, Lessie Hoover,1929. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Lot 501 - Thorpe Family Papers,1914-1919. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Lot 505 - Life Insurance Policy, Harold Thomas,1927. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Lot 508 - Paul K. Yeonas Papers,1921-1923. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Lot 510 - Application for Ration Currency, Woodrow Batton,1943. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Lot 511 - Notification of Birth Registration, wright Family,1935-1942. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Lot 511a - Yount Family Papers,1922-1948. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Lot 512 - Death Notice and Photograph, M. J. Brady,1924. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Lot 514 - Joseph C. Hough Papers,1911-1920. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Lot 527 - Floyd J. Oliver Papers,1949-1963. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Lot 537 - Mary Cooke Papers,1923. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Lot 538 - A. W. Fairfield Papers,1918-1919. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Lot 544 - Roberts Family Papers,1917-1937. (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Lot 547 - Deeds,1939. (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Lot 549 - Martha Jane Owen Papers,915-1926. (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Lot 550 - Ayers Family Papers,1934-1945. (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Lot 551 - Harry L. Echols,1924-1931. (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Lot 553 - Joseph Mathesion Papers,1921-1931. (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Lot 554 - Miller Family Papers, Correspondence,1934-1936. (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Lot 554 - Miller Family Papers, Correspondence,1937-1940. (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Lot 554 - Miller Family Papers, Correspondence,1942-1943. (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Lot 554 - Miller Family Papers, Correspondence,n.d.. (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Lot 554 - Miller Family Papers, Correspondence, Leon J. Brodsky,1938-1940. (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Lot 554 - Miller Family Papers, Miscellaneous,1938-1942. (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Lot 556 - Agreement,1904. (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Lot 566 - Deed,1931. (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Lot 569 - Deed of Trust,1934. (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Lot 570 - William J. Fowler Papers,1919-1925. (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Lot 571- Deed,1916. (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Lot 576 - Life Insurance Certificate,1922. (See also oversized Box 21) (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Lot 579 - H. W. Johnston Papers,1929. (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Lot 580 - Deed,1916. (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Lot 581 - Effie Lankford Papers,1924. (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Lot 582 - Application for Life Insurance,1944. (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Lot 583 - Marshall Henry Lynn Papers,1946. (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Lot 585 - Ten Men Business Club Bylaws,n.d.. (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Lot 587 - Deed of Trust,1922. (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Lot 594 - Lewis Worrell Papers,1929. (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Lot 596 - Pulley Family Papers,1918-1947. (See also oversized Box 21) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Lot 597 - J. T. Rayfield Papers,1917-1918. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Lot 598 - Deed and Map,1910. (See also oversized Box 21) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Lot 603 - Motley Family Papers,1927-1946. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Lot 604 - Savage Family Papers,1941-1944. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Lot 605 - Deed,1933. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Lot 607 - Reuben Barton Jr., Correspondence,1944-1945. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Lot 608 - Papers of Ernest Linwood Vaughan Jr.,1942-1943. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Lot 609 - Joyner Family Papers,1916-1944. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Lot 615 - George R. Walden Papers,1941. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Lot 616 - Mary C. Cherry Pension Certificate,1918-1920. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Lot 617 - Louther Family Papers,1941-1942. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Lot 631 - O. D. Henrhy Papers,1944-1949. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Lot 632 - Roy G. Wariner Papers,1944. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Lot 634 - Butler Family Papers,1916-1946. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Lot 635 - Abbott Family Correspondence,1943. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Lot 636 - Barclay Lyon Papers,1942-1949. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Lot 637 - M. M. Wunder Papers,1940. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Lot 650 - Insurance Policies,1945-1948. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Lot 655 - R. Lee Parker Papers,1935. (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Lot 663 - Mollie Hammon Papers,1910-1922. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Lot 664 - Nora E. Jefferson Papers,1930. (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Lot 665 - James S. Perry Papers,1927. (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Lot 666 - T. T. Springfield,1928. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Lot 668 - William L. Whitaker Papers,1947. (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Lot 669 - Horace A. Bradley Papers,1945-1951. (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Lot 670 - Edward K. Sheppard Papers,1944. (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Lot 671 - Butler Family Papers,1944-1950. (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Lot 674 - Elizabeth A. Hatton Papers,1936-1957. (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Lot 675 - John J. Matheny Papers,1945. (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Lot 676 - Murton E. Trent Papers,1939-1944. (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Lot 677 - Vernon C. Stafford Papers,1858-1946. (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Lot 680 - Life Insurance Policy,1941. (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Lot 682 - Oliver A. Ackiss Papers,1925-1932. (See also oversized Box 21) (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Lot 685 - Deeds,1908-1941. (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Lot 686 - William R. Awe Papers,1939-1946. (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Lot 687 - Luzena F. Bakers Papers-Correspondence,1923-1925. (1 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Lot 687 - Luzena F. Bakers Papers-Correspondence,1926-1933. (2 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Lot 687 - Luzena F. Bakers Papers-Correspondence,1934. (3 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Lot 687 - Luzena F. Bakers Papers-Correspondence,1935. (4 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Lot 687 - Luzena F. Bakers Papers-Miscellaneous,1927-1945. (5 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Lot 688 - Balfour Family Papers,1940-1950. (Box 14, Folder 1)